doctortushy.com 2018-06-07

# DoctorTushy.com

We appreciate your use of DoctorTushy.com and understand that you may be concerned about your privacy when accessing sites on the Internet. Following is our privacy statement, which is designed to provide you with information on how we obtain, use and disseminate your information. If you have any questions regarding this statement, please contact us at [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

Information Obtained

When you join DoctorTushy.com, you will be asked for some personal information to complete your signup. The information you provide is not made available to the public or any third party other than CCBill.com, which processes memberships for DoctorTushy.com. 

Minors

Individuals under the age of 18 should not access this site. If we discover that a minor has joined the site or is viewing the site, we will move to block their access to the best of our ability using technology reasonably available. 

Use of Cookies

We use "cookies" to identify how individuals use our site and to facilitate modifications and improvements to our site for your benefit. A "cookie" is a small piece of information that is placed on the hard drive of your computer so we can identify you when you access the site. The use of cookies is a common practice on the Internet. You can avoid the use of cookies on your site by disabling all cookies, typically by accessing the Internet options bar on your browser. We solely monitor activity on this site. Once you leave the site, we do not monitor your activity.

Sale of Member Information

We do NOT sell, share or give away any information about you. 

Billing Information

We do NOT sell, share or give away any information regarding your credit card or other payment source. We do use a third party to process your membership payments, but neither that party nor ourselves provides such information to any third party. We reserve the right to provide such information to any law enforcement officials that make a legally binding request for said information.

Email Information

From time-to-time, we may forward information to you regarding site developments, special promotions, press releases and other information. Your email will not be used for any other purpose with the exception of customer service responses. We will not provide, sell or share your email address to any third parties. If you wish to avoid receiving occasional mailings from us, simply opt-out of our email list as indicated on the site.

Linking to Third Party Sites  
This site may contain links to other sites not controlled by DoctorTushy.com. Please note that such sites may have privacy policies that differ from ours. We have no control over any personal information that you provide to these sites and you should review their privacy policies before providing any personal information.  
Privacy Policy Changes

DoctorTushy.com reserves the right to change this privacy policy at any time. You are encouraged to check back with the site to ascertain whether any changes have occurred since you last reviewed the policy. 

Refund Policy

We do not offer any refunds on memberships to DoctorTushy.com.

Contact

If you have any questions regarding the above Policy Statement, please contact us at [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)
